Benjamin Windsor

I'm a creative designer currently residing in London. My experience spans across both digital and web. I'm knowledgeable in the Adobe creative suite specifically Ai, Ps, Id & Xd alongside a strong understanding of front end languages html5 & css3.

I complete deliverables in a time efficient manner and am a team player. I create visual experiences with user centric design always at the forefront.



Experience

Digital Designer May 2021 - Present (+4

Sep 2019 - Sep 2020

Sep 2017 - Feb 2018

Vanarama

Creative Recruiter

Major Players

Front End Web Dev

Hastings Direct

Contact

(+44) 7748 472708

benjaminwindsor.com

benjaminawindsor@gmail.com

Education

2.1 BSc Hons - Creative Media Technology Leeds Beckett University - July 2015

Interests

I'm happiest when creating stuff and an enthusiast of many things. Outside of work I enjoy making music, illustrations and experimental cooking. Alongside watching Formula I, Uber rating 4.9.

Skills

Artworking

Adobe Creative Suite

A Keen eye for design

High understanding of UI

Verstaile and adaptable

Stakeholder management